math24.net 2019-06-20

# Privacy Policy

Last Updated: Mar 01, 2019

At Math24.net, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you visit Math24.net, and how we use and safeguard your information. 

### Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP address, your ISP (internet service provider), the browser you used to visit our site, the time you visited our site, the pages you visited throughout our site and other click-stream data. The log files do not contain any information which allows to identify you personally.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

We use cookies and other tracking technologies to make our website easier to use and to better tailor it to your interests and needs. Cookies are small data files placed on your computer or other internet-enabled device that enable our features and functionality. Other tracking technologies, such as web beacons and pixels work similarly to cookies, placing small data files on your device that monitor your website activity. 

We use _Google Analytics_ to monitor site usage in order to improve the quality of the pages. Google Analytics provides statistical data only for website management. Google Analytics use cookies. See: [Google Analytics cookie usage](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage), [Google privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

We also use third party advertisements on Math24.net. These third-party ad servers or ad networks (such as Google through the _Google AdSense_ program) use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Math24.net and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies or web beacons) may also be used by our site’s third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site. Math24.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).

You can allow, avoid or remove cookies installed by using your Internet browser configuration options. Blocking cookies might prevent some pages from working properly.

Disclosure of Information

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

### Security

Sensitive and private data exchange between the website and its users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the “last updated” date at the beginning of the Privacy Policy. 

### Contact Us

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@math24.net](mailto:support@math24.net).

This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Reject [Read More](https://www.math24.net/privacy-policy/)
